<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bdmeter on Bdmeter News</title>
    <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bdmeter on Bdmeter News</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://news.bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://news.bdmeter.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Panama canal is facing a serious challenge due to a severe drought</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/news/2023/08/2023-08-20-panama-canal-dried-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/news/2023/08/2023-08-20-panama-canal-dried-up/</guid>
      <description>Global economy crisis due to panama canal stoppage The Panama Canal is one of the most important trade routes in the world, connecting the Atlantic and Pacific oceans and allowing ships to save time and money by avoiding the long detour around South America. However, the canal is facing a serious challenge due to a severe drought that has reduced the water levels in the artificial lake that supplies the locks that lift and lower the ships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Lake Mead and Lake Powell Water Levels Are Changing and Why It Matters</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/news/2023/08/2023-08-17-lake-mead-lake-powell-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/news/2023/08/2023-08-17-lake-mead-lake-powell-changes/</guid>
      <description>How Lake Mead and Lake Powell Water Levels Are Changing and Why It Matters Lake Mead and Lake Powell are two of the largest reservoirs in the United States and the main storage units of the Colorado River system, which provides water to about 40 million people and 5.5 million acres of farmland in seven states and Mexico. However, both lakes have been suffering from a prolonged drought that has reduced their water levels to historically low levels, threatening the water supply, hydropower generation, recreation and ecosystem of the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should Ukraine Give Up Territory for NATO Membership?</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/news/2023/08/2023-08-17-ukraine-give-up-territory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/news/2023/08/2023-08-17-ukraine-give-up-territory/</guid>
      <description>Should Ukraine Give Up Territory for NATO Membership? The recent suggestion by a senior NATO official that Ukraine could consider ceding some of its disputed territories to Russia in exchange for joining the military alliance has sparked a heated debate among experts, politicians and the public. The idea, which was quickly retracted and apologized for by the official, was met with strong opposition and criticism from the Ukrainian government and society, who see it as a betrayal of their sovereignty and national interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sitemap</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-16-sitemap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-16-sitemap/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maui&#39;s Wildfires Rage On, Challenging Firefighting Efforts</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/news/2023/08/2023-08-12-unveiling-the-mythical-fury/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/news/2023/08/2023-08-12-unveiling-the-mythical-fury/</guid>
      <description>Unveiling the Mythical Fury: Maui&amp;rsquo;s Wildfires Rage On, Challenging Firefighting Efforts Maui, August 12, 2023 — The picturesque paradise of Maui is facing an unprecedented natural catastrophe as wildfires continue to rage across the island, leaving authorities and residents grappling with a unique set of challenges. Unlike typical wildfire scenarios, the flames have taken on an almost mythic quality, prompting locals to dub them &amp;ldquo;Pele&amp;rsquo;s Breath,&amp;rdquo; in reference to the Hawaiian goddess of fire and volcanoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disaster dealy wildfire acroos Maui</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/news/2023/08/2023-08-11-maui-wildfires-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/news/2023/08/2023-08-11-maui-wildfires-death/</guid>
      <description>Headlines Six people have been killed in wildfires in Maui. Broadband internet outage across Hawaii. Violent wind across Hawaii from Maui burning. 150,000 gallons of water spray dropped yet to stop burning but no outcome yet. US Miltery top on the race to deploy firefighters to save Maui and Big Islands. Copast guards from US is saving life to do water rescue. People run into the ocean to save life. Fires is continuing and not under control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-17-contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-17-contact/</guid>
      <description>You can write us directly. Our email address bdmeter.info@gmail.com
**Our Address:
**22 W 34th St, 301, New York, NY 10001, US
We are very happy to support our customers. Feel free to send us an email and call us direct to get support. Our support team is working from Monday-Friday 9 AM – 5 PM. Visit us and fix a schedule before your visit. Our location:
Address: 22 W 34th St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-17-privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-17-privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Who we are We are Bdmeter News, located in NYC, United States. We are one of the largest information services providers of real-time global information, technology, business, innovations, changes, ideas, thinking, and the future.
Comments When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine Policy</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/04/2023-04-05-vaccine-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/04/2023-04-05-vaccine-policy/</guid>
      <description>We are Bdmeter news department, a fully online base information service and tech company. Bdmeter always advises all of its employees working remotely to ensure Covid-19 vaccination with booster dose to ensure life security. We aren&amp;rsquo;t limited to accepting only vaccinated people into our organization because Bdmeter is only online based, and no close contact is related to our organization&amp;rsquo;s terms.
So, whoever is working with , is not limited to working from home if he/she is vaccinated/not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real-time industry information for your business &amp; industry</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-30-real-time-news-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-30-real-time-news-update/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earn with news online</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-26-earn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-26-earn/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not easy to earn and make money. We have a team of industrialist Technology and businessman was thinking a lot how people can make money online in terms of business and industry. We why are digging deeper to find out what is matter and how can we make money. Finally we are here in result that we can make money by sharing our knowledge stills and ideas with people all over the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-20-newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-20-newsletter/</guid>
      <description>Subscribe for live news newsletter Email: Click here for subscribe </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-19-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-19-community/</guid>
      <description>We Bdmeter Technology are combining our community to contribute to the global technological revolution as well as build skilled manpower.
Join the Bdmeter community to share your skills, ideas, and knowledge. We believe in you, and your innovative ideations will help our community to grow a better future.
How to join the Bdmeter community To join Bdmeter community, sign up here
Click here to Sign up
Due to high number of requests, we are unavailable for certain period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-17-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-17-about/</guid>
      <description>About Us Our Story We are Bdmeter News, We are a team of Journalist and Bloggers, and News Specialists have started our jouney in June 2021. We are an organization of live news moderator, analyzer to represent news in a way means more authentic and reliable.
We are driven by values Our team work makes us important to the people, to the industry and to our communities. Our value added contents are helping over miilions readers worldwide to learn different terms of business and industry to implement those in practical field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-17-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2023/03/2023-03-17-home/</guid>
      <description>Real time global information of Business Industry &amp;amp; Technology We believe share knowledge with all of us should be free and open for all as like open source code.
LEARN MORE
SEE ALL LATEST
Business Update Grow your business faster than ever. Learn more with bdmeter.info
Industry Update Bdmeter is the industry leader to share more valuable content that is useful for money industry leaders.
Technology Update Latest technology Updates help business owner to implement new ideas, innovations and help us to know which suits our industry most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About BDM</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2020/11/2020-11-21-about-bdm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2020/11/2020-11-21-about-bdm/</guid>
      <description>About Us Our Story We are Bdmeter, We are a team of friends and most are Engineers, Technologists, Architects, Builders, and Specialists was thinking louder in last 2018 to develop something that can help people. Then we have descided to start a blogsite and we are the Authors from his own position of work. Then we have started our jouney in October 2018. We are trying to help our communities to learn something really important to develop our business, industry, socienty, environment, shelter, health, safety all together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifestyle</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2020/11/2020-11-21-lifestyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2020/11/2020-11-21-lifestyle/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2020/11/2020-11-19-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2020/11/2020-11-19-community/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Culture</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2020/11/2020-11-19-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2020/11/2020-11-19-culture/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2020/11/2020-11-19-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2020/11/2020-11-19-future/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2020/11/2020-11-19-privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.bdmeter.info/page/2020/11/2020-11-19-privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Who we are Our website address is https://news.bdmeter.info.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it Comments When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
